### HTTP Injector Privacy Policy

Last modified: November 3, 2022

### 1\. PRIVACY POLICY

Evozi PLT. ("Evozi") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to data collected by Evozi through www.evozi.com and the software/apps provided and owned by Evozi (collectively, the "Site"), our mobile and desktop apps (the "Apps") and all related sites, widgets, tools, apps, data, software, APIs and other services provided by Evozi (the “Services”)

Evozi reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting without advance notice to you. Such revisions shall be effective to you immediately upon posting. Notice of material changes to either document will be posted on the website’s homepage and/or will be provided by e-mailing you or notifying you upon login about these changes. However, Evozi encourages you to check this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service often for updates.

This Privacy Policy is a part of the terms and conditions which are set forth in our Terms of Service. Any terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning given in the Terms of Service. Both the Privacy Policy and Terms of Service are legally binding on all users and you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service.

Please read all information as provided below. Evozi welcomes any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or if you do not understand any information about how we collect, maintain, use or disclose personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"). Any such questions or comments, or if more information regarding any item not listed below is needed, should be submitted via email to [\[email protected\]](https://httpinjector.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) .

At Evozi, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Evozi and how it is used.

### 2\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION.

You **do not** need to provide any personal information to use the Services

When you use our native apps, we may collect certain information in addition to the information mentioned elsewhere in this Policy. We may use mobile analytics software (Play/App Store app statistics or crash reporting) to send crash information to our developers so that we can fix bugs rapidly. Some platforms (such as the Google Play Store or the Apple App Store) may also collect aggregate, anonymous statistics, such as which type of devices and operating systems are most commonly used (e.g. percentage of Android 11.x vs Android 12.x), the total number of installs, total number of uninstalls, and the total number of active users, and may be governed by the privacy policy and terms and conditions of Google Play Store or Apple App Store.

### 3\. DATA RETENTION

HTTP Injector does not collect or retain data about your browsing activity while you are connected to the VPN Services.

### 4\. DEVICE PERMISSIONS FOR PERSONAL DATA ACCESS

HTTP Injector Android and iOS apps may request certain permissions that allow it to access the user’s device data as described below.

These permissions must be granted by the user before the respective information can be accessed. Once the permission has been given, it can be revoked by the user at any time in device settings.

Please note that revoking of such permissions might impact the proper functioning of the app.

##### Android App

STORAGE PERMISSION:The app may need to read or write configuration files (.ehi) files on the device. The files are processed locally and no user's device files is shared or collected.

QUERY ALL PACKAGES PERMISSION:Package names are used when establishing VPN connection to filter certain app traffic and move it outside the VPN tunnel. Icons are used for UI purposes only. Since it's an install-type permission unfortunately there is no way to make it 'toggleable' for people who don't need apps filter/split tunnelling. The app neither collects nor shares any information about device installed apps.

##### iOS App

PERMISSION TO SAVE VPN PROFILE:Required to access the current Wi-Fi SSID, when the Network Protection feature is enabled.

HTTP Injector is a professional VPN tool to browse the Internet privately and securely with multiple protocol and tunneling technologies build into one app

##### Services

##### About Us

* [\[email protected\]](https://httpinjector.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

##### Contact Info

* [\[email protected\]](https://httpinjector.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

© 2023 Evozi. All Rights Reserved.
